{
  "data": [
    {
      "quizTitle": "Quiz One",
      "quizData": [
        {
          "question": "What’s the biggest planet in our solar system?",
          "options": ["Jupiter", "Saturn", "Neptune", "Mercury"],
          "correct_option": "Jupiter"
        },
        {
          "question": "What attraction in India is one of the famus in the world?",
          "options": ["Chand Minar", "Taj Mahal", "Stadium"],
          "correct_option": "Taj Mahal"
        },
        {
          "question": "What land animal can open its mouth the widest?",
          "options": ["Alligator", "Crocodile", "Baboon", "Hippo"],
          "correct_option": "Hippo"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the largest animal on Earth?",
          "options": [
            "The African elephant",
            "The blue whale",
            "The sperm whale",
            "The giant squid"
          ],
          "correct_option": "The blue whale"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the only flying mammal?",
          "options": [
            "The bat",
            "The flying squirrel",
            "The bald eagle",
            "The colugo"
          ],
          "correct_option": "The bat"
        }
      ],
      "isAttempted": false,
      "marks": 0
    },
    {
      "quizTitle": "Quiz Two",
      "quizData": [
        {
          "question": "After “Thursday” comes what day?",
          "options": ["Wednesday", "Saturday", "Friday", "Sunday"],
          "correct_option": "Friday"
        },
        {
          "question": "What does a plant need the most to live?",
          "options": ["Sun, water, and air", "Dark light", "A friend", "Music"],
          "correct_option": "Sun, water, and air"
        },
        {
          "question": "What rhymes with “rat”?",
          "options": ["Run", "Jump", "Pig", "Bat"],
          "correct_option": "Bat"
        }
      ],
      "isAttempted": false,
      "marks": 0
    },
    {
      "quizTitle": "Quiz Three",
      "quizData": [
        {
          "question": "What word also starts with the same sound as “ball”?",
          "options": ["Baby", "Dog", "Apple", "Cat"],
          "correct_option": "Dog"
        },
        {
          "question": "Red and blue mixed together make what color?",
          "options": ["Yellow", "Green", "Purple", "Orange"],
          "correct_option": "Purple"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the color of the sun?",
          "options": ["Green", "Brown", "Purple", "Yellow"],
          "correct_option": "Yellow"
        }
      ],
      "isAttempted": false,
      "marks": 0
    }
  ]
}
